everyone needs to be invited we cannot
create a new elitist system and expect
not to repeat many of the mistakes of
the current system corruption greed etc
there is and will be room for everyone
but we are only going to appeal to the
exact right people at the time currently
it is mainly just me imperfectly doing
the things that need to be done within
my own limitations
this means it does not look super
professional and isn't that perfect
because my videos are not edited my
website is free and easy version of Wix
because that is what I am currently
capable of in the past this imperfection
would have stopped me didn't stop me and
all of my past business ideas I did not
want to feel or to be seen it is seen as
wrong or look like a fool
I'm so over that now or rather
I'm getting over it daily I am
imperfectly failing in the right
direction and I will not be giving up on
this project unless something even
better comes along and so far I've not
seen anything even out of wit once I
could see the perfection in my own and
projects and perfection a light went on
I am exactly who I am supposed to be to
create this this project is exactly how
and where it needs to be to draw in the
right people who will my message appeal
to those who are done with the window
dressing of our current capitalist
system that insists on professionalism
and perfection at the cost of innovation
and authenticity people who believe
mistakes are allowed to be made
professionally and in this I will draw
in these exact people people who don't
need the traditional hierarchy of
leadership and people who will allow
each other to fail than repair and move
forward together we are not
incentivizing in the old way we are
creating a new way in which individuals
do what they love as much or as little
as they want the joy is in the doing so
little external motivation is needed
this will appeal to the people who have
something they love to do and for some
of those people the thing they love to
do is exactly what we need is an
organization currently we do not have a
traditional product we are not yet
solving our complex problems with
solutions that will draw in the masses
we instead have this product of hope
hope for a better world and getting to
participate in the creation
we have the product that appeals to the
to a very specific and amazing human our
imperfection is perfect because it will
draw in the exact people we need to
start with ie these people what they
have in common
one these people can see the beauty of
what I am trying to create within my
imperfect communication methods people
who can see beyond the picture on the
cover to the true story inside to people
who want to work and pay to do that work
for the greater good that is the mega
co-operators will be our starting
culture three people who seek and are
authentic not fake perfect or striving
for the same ideal of perfection people
who will allow each other to be
different and understand that does not
make us better or worse just different
and as these people with mega
cooperation in common come on board they
also bring their unique gifts and
talents as well some of these people
will be able to edit videos and will be
better at communicating our message more
eloquently for the masses are you
bringing in other people computer
computer people who will create
necessary betas in a new professional
website these people will improve our
image and help create the actual
products and systems that will bring in
the people who need the pretty book
cover ie professionalism people who are
less cooperative and people who may not
have been comfortable with the level of
diversity and authenticity we originally
started with but are now drawn in due to
the features and benefits of our then
existing products as we create tools to
improve our lives then people who want
their lives improved come onboard as
they find out about us and it resonates
with them everything is voluntary and we
naturally appeal to those who we are
ready for once we are ready for them we
want everyone who wants to be a part of
creating this as they want to be a part
of creating it I hope that I did this
subject justice and communicated what
I'm trying to say but I also know that
is communicated in the right way for the
right people who may help me make it
even better by pointing out what is
unclear and what questions it brought up
for them thank you